Greetings, comrades.  On the forty-eighth
and forty-ninth parts of the retelling of Manhwa
Alice.  Don't be lazy to like and
write comments.  Enjoy
watching everyone.
And the previous part ended
quite interestingly.  Somewhere in a
remote, lifeless area
underground in a laboratory, a security guard
called the main character's mother.  At the same
time, Zhu began to worry, because
for some reason his mother had not called him lately.
Usually she would call once a month
, but it's been 3 days now and there's been
no news.  Well, well, anything can happen.  And yes, it would seem so
, but over the last 5 years, mother has never
missed a day.  Then why does
n't Ju call her first?
But the guy already
did it yesterday.  Even so, my mother didn't pick up the phone.   She
was probably busy.  but she didn't even
call back at night.  Well, yeah, in any case, Joe
should have waited a little longer.  Maybe I'll
get a message from her today.
After listening to the teachers, the main character
went out to spend his usual day in
the hope of a call from his mother.  But
evening came, and he still hadn’t arrived.
Besides, her phone was always on
answering machine.
What happened to her?  The son is worried.
Unexpectedly, Kaiden suggested that the boy
go see her personally.  If you're that
worried, then it's okay to go
visit your mom.  Moreover, her silence is
very suspicious.  So what will
Joey do?  A little later, the friends
visited our hero’s house, but
they did not meet the owner himself.  It
was somehow boring in this room without Jiu.
Meanwhile, Jiu was already on the plane, heading
to his mother’s work.  Everyone was
comfortable except Kaidan.  Unfortunately, cargo weighing more than
7 kg had to be left in the cargo
compartment.  Since the teenager had already been
to his mother’s rented apartment once, he
knew where he needed to go.  Now all that
was needed was to press the
doorbell, and Mom would open the
door herself.  True, after several attempts,
nothing happened.  Maybe mom is
n't home?  However, if so, then the little one
needs to lift Kaidin to the door lock.  And
yes, now.  Wow, that's heavy.  Well, a
thief's life is not easy, but
picking a lock is not a big deal
.  It's amazing what
cats' naughty paws are capable of.  Once
inside, the heroes found themselves in a rather
empty and very modest room.
Did Mama Ju really live here all this time?   It's
so cramped here.  By the way, there was already
ten layers of dust accumulated here.  It was as if no
one had ever lived in this apartment.  But no, the
main character clearly remembered that his mother had
settled here.  Then how does he
explain all this accumulation of dust?  So
the guy himself doesn't know.  However, it is
certain that his mother sent him parcels from this address.  So there
could only be one explanation for everything.  The woman
used this address to
hide.  At that moment, Ju
remembered how, as a child, his mother had
calmed him down about his illness.  And,
besides, she made him happy that she
seemed to have found a way to learn more about her
son’s body.  But for this the baby will have to
live away from the mother.
Everything will be fine with him.  The main
character couldn’t say no, because he sincerely believed
his mother.  Several years later, Yujo
visited the baby.  She said that in the
place where she works there are a lot of
strong people, and it seems that her mother
could not leave them alone.  So will my
son be okay if he lives
alone for a little while longer?  Seeing his mother
shaking, Ju squeezed her hand tighter and
promised that everything would be fine with him.
Therefore, mom can continue to do what she
thinks is right.  Kaidan pulled the guy out of his memories
.  So, where does
his mother work?  Well, as Joe knows, it's at the
pharmaceutical company Oin.
She settled there to heal his
body.  Hmm, now that makes me
suspicious.  Then Trinity should start its
search from there.  At the same time, the
head guard continued to interrogate
Kanya John.  Why did the doctor steal
the samples?  But the woman did not understand what
these questions were about.  She already said that she didn’t
crawl.  And how can you remove something that is
immediately disposed of?
That's how it is.  And what will she say to the fact that
the guard received one sample today,
which from Yujeong's report was disposed of
several months ago?  Wow!
The specimen is still alive.  Stop.  What?
The doctor doesn’t understand something, how could he
be alive?  It's true that it's
time to stop trying to act like an innocent lamb.  The
management has evidence.
The sample caught in the morning himself gave
Juice's mother away red-handed.  Therefore, it is better for the woman to
start telling the truth while the guard is
so calm.  Oh, what is this Morocco?
It turns out the doctor plans to remain silent until the very
end.  Well, that's not a problem,
because soon someone who
can read minds will visit the lab.  And Yujung is
very familiar with this procedure.
If he resists to the last, the
awakened one will have to apply
a lot of force, and this is fraught with death.
Moreover, you can go crazy in front of her.
By the way, the guard forgot to add the
sample that was caught.  Before
answering the questions, he experienced
a little pain, after which he told
everything as it happened, and that Kanyu Jojong was the
first to suggest that he run away.
It's an interesting situation, isn't
it?  Eventually, the truth about the
doctor's actions was revealed.  Soon
she will definitely not be alive.  But Jiu, he can
cope without his mom.  Well of course, her
boy is very strong.  Although no, from the
very beginning he didn’t need his
mother.  After all, back then on the beach, Yujo
abandoned her duties as a mother.  And
now she couldn't even say goodbye to
her only boy.  When the
main character arrived at the Oin corporation,
he was told that a man
named Kanyu John did not work for them, and was
not even listed on the
employee list.  But this is impossible.  Joe is
sure she worked here.
Suddenly the same security guard called out to the guy
.  He accidentally overheard the
conversation.  So the student is looking for Dr.
Kanya DJohn, right?  And who is she to him
?  Well, mom.  It’s strange, because the
doctor had no relatives in the employee database
.  Therefore,
another way to put pressure on the traitor arose.   That
is why the man promised to take his
son to his mother.  Let him follow
him.  Yeah, right.  This task is becoming more and more interesting with each passing hour
.
Meanwhile, Kaidan and Kartain were sitting on the
roof and discussing how this whole
situation seemed somehow unnatural.   A
fake apartment, a mother who
hid the father's truth for several years.
Oh, I hope to God that everything works out.  I don't
want to worry about
Jivu again.  And what?  Oh, how annoying.  Oh, that's
surprising to hear from you.  Already in
the car, Zhu tried to find out more about his
mother’s work.  As it turns out, she really is a
warrior, but she is conducting
research in a separate center, where
they are actually headed.  After some
time, the car drove out of the city and
cut through the lifeless land, which
could not help but arouse suspicion in our
hero.  And how much longer do they have to travel?  The man
said it was not far.  Damn, this little guy really got on my nerves
.  Should I close my mouth
or not?  Suddenly, one of the
sixes pulled out some kind of syringe and, with a precise
movement, almost plunged it into the guy’s neck.
And what was it?  Well, sleeping pills.  If
the boy hadn't twitched, he would have
fallen asleep long ago, but now a fist would send him to sleep
.  But it was purely Joe's reaction that
stopped him.  Really, why did the attacker have
so much strength?  He was clearly an unusual person,
and as soon as he loosened his grip, his fist
shattered the car window.  There was
no way to resolve this peacefully, so the main
character launched a counterattack and threw the
first enemy out into the open.
That one flew by, of course, spectacularly.  The bespectacled man
got out of the car.  He figured it out, that
little woke one, and he was [ __ ]
right.  But now it’s clear why
the doctor so carefully hid her
son.  But the little brat shouldn't let his guard
down, because at that very second the
second sucker started shooting at him with a
pistol.  Luckily, his super speed
allowed him to easily avoid contact
with the bullets, which meant it took Ju
a few moments to close the distance.
He knocked the gun away, dodged the lunge and
landed a well-aimed kick to the bastard's stomach.
The last one went straight to the head, but
he discarded his comrade like useless
trash.  Well, the doctor's son turned out to be a
good one.  Answer, do you really know
my mother?  What?  I'm asking, do you really
know my mother and why did you bring her here?
Oh, how hungry I am.  That's why it irritates the man so much
.  Even in such a situation
he remains calm.  They look down on people
as if they were some kind of pathetic little
bugs, and think that the world belongs
only to them, while they do
n’t value ordinary citizens at all.  This speech was illogical,
because the Bruiser speaks as if he himself
is not awakened.  Gradually,
strength began to flow into the guard's hand.  And,
honestly, he was surprised by the speed of
Shkler’s strength.  The world would go crazy if
everyone had such abilities.  But the
blond guy doesn't have to worry.
No one will kill him, because there are
still many questions left for him.  However,
he
certainly won't like the methods by which the answers will be obtained.  The big man waved
his hand, and the ground cracked in his path
.  Every attack was
directed at Ju.  However, it was time to
stop dodging, so
the guy charged his fist and knocked the glasses off the
dark-skinned man's arrogant face.  True, his
blow was stopped, which means the guy is
definitely an unusual worker.  Hey, what
organization are you in?  Where
can you find such smart people?  But
no one planned to answer him.  Well, it did
n't matter now anyway.  In any
case, the big guy will find out everything when he
catches the kid.  With this phrase, he took out
some kind of device and applied it to
his neck.  A certain substance began to enter the bloodstream
, causing the body to
literally swell.  What the
hell is this anyway?  Is there anything
that allows you to become stronger instantly?
But Ju didn't need to think about that, about the
mutated enemy.  Well, are you frozen?  Ah,
I think you were confused by my appearance.   Even though
I look ridiculous,
I managed to catch hundreds of
awakened ones this way.
Now it became more difficult to avoid hitting the man
.  In that moment, the hand was a
couple of centimeters away from Zhio, and then the ground
shook from the impact.  Fortunately, the speed
still allowed him to stay alive, but there was
no time to catch his breath, because
the mutant did not slow down and
continued to raise dust in the area with his fist.  When
the sand settled on the ground, the guard
was again amazed that the little one had dodged.  His
speed is truly amazing.  Who
taught him this?  Because no
organization can boast of
skills like Ju's.  Although they will still have
time to discuss this.
Remind me, you wanted to see
your mother.  Well then, you
can surrender to me and I will bring you to
Dr. Kanyu John.  But will
she even recognize you after such a long period of
brainwashing?
These provocations have killed all of Zhu's previous
fear, but he can stop pretending to be
tough.  Another blow missed, and the
car was blown off the road.  Having guessed the moment, the
main character delivered a blow to the freak’s face.   He did
n't even realize when the little one had time.
But immediately afterward, the man's body
began to absorb tons of damage in every possible place
, and he couldn't respond in any way,
because he simply couldn't see the enemy's movements.  In
the end, Joe used his
signature move and punched right through the big guy's body,
thereby knocking him out and
emerging victorious in the fight.
While on the ground, the guard couldn't
catch up.  Where the hell did
this monster come from?  I'm asking for the last time.
Where is my mom?  And when did he even manage to get there?
Although the boy is strong, he is naive.   Is
it really just a coincidence that
he came looking for a doctor right now?
The guard said that he would take the little one, since he
was planning to do so anyway.  But no
need.  Let him just tell me where it is
.  So, even if he tells, the
boy still won’t find the secret
research center.  He
doesn't even have an exact address.  Having thought it all over in
his head, the guy agreed to do so.
Actually, it won't end there.  And
in the laboratory itself, the purple-haired
woman watched as her test subject
overheated, without revealing anything
special.  Perhaps because he escaped
not long ago.  It was Ms. Laila,
whose mind reading specification.
She just rummaged around in the head of the
awakened one, and he, as you can see,
died.  And next in line was
Dr. Kanyu John, who helped
the deceased escape.  Oh, how Layla is looking forward to
meeting her.  We need to visit her quickly
.  In another room, Mama Zhu had already
come to terms with death, but they still would
n’t let her go.  thoughts of having to
forget my son.  Oh, hi.  You are Yoojung, aren't you?  I'm
Laila.  The very same awakened one,
specializing in mental
abilities.  And although people call Layla
awakened, she prefers to be a
doctor mentalist.  After all, she loves to
talk about what’s on her
patients’ minds.  Well, the woman is ready.  It's time
to start their conversation.  But, Yujo, there is no need to be
afraid.  Layla will not use her full
power.  After all, every person has their own
limit, after which the mind begins to
collapse.
And his mentalist madly enjoys
defining it
slowly.  She also enjoys watching the
countless expressions on people's faces
when they reach their limits.  You are a
doctor, so you probably understand me,
right?  At the same time, the guard brought Joo to the
object, and he bets his life that he did not
deceive, and Doctor Yujung is
inside.  So, mom works there, what does
she do?  Well, inside the guard,
hope was seething.  After all, as soon as a little one sets
foot on their territory, how can he
meet Laila?  Of course, this
bean is crazy, but there is no doubt about her abilities
.  As if unexpectedly,
Ju's hand fell on his contented face.  He
thought of this, but before the Big Man could even [ __ ] out
anything, his
skull was fried.  It's lucky that
Kaidan recently taught the guy this technique.  Well, now it's time to find mom.
With slow, confident movements, the
main character headed towards the security post.
The men politely asked him to leave
here, but Joe seemed to have come here in
search of one person.  And what kind?
Dr. Kanyu John.  Without wasting a second,
one of the guys pointed a gun at the
teenager, while the other rushed to
urgently report the former guest.
Watching this commotion, Joe became convinced
that his mother was definitely being held here, and
that, by the way, Layla had begun
to work on her.  The woman is really
mentally strong.
I passed the fourth level.  Oh well, soon she'll start to lose her
mind and start talking on her own
.  I wonder what Dr.
Kanyu John is hiding?  I'll
find out everything anyway, and you'll die, losing your mind.  But do you
have to be so faithful to what
you defend there?  Come on, surrender.  If
you tell us everything, we can make the
process more comfortable.  But, obviously,
the mother will not allow the traveler to find out about
her son.  However, the process was abruptly
interrupted.  Seeing the intruder, Yujeong was
stunned.  [ __ ], how dare you?  I'm
sorry, this is urgent.  Some kid
came here looking for Dr. Kanyu John.
What did you just say?  And the child who
could come for Yud John and could only be
No, no.  June wasn't supposed to
come here when suddenly the woman's face
was imprinted on the metal table.  Well, let him
post it.  Who else has come?
Damn, he's silent again.  Okay, then Laila
will go and meet this
child in person.  And Mom still tried not to
believe that this was her Joo.  And again a
separate room, where this time the
main character was sitting surrounded by two
guards.  What kind of place is this?
What is mom doing here?
A mentalist suddenly burst into the room and she was like, "Well,
[ __ ], I'm so happy to see this cute little guy."
Without further ado, the girl immediately began
to use her power on the guest, which
could not be hidden from Ju's eyes.  So, will
you tell Nuni what connects you with
Dr. Kanyu John?  The guy clearly
understood that the force sitting opposite him was
not yet being used to its maximum.  In general, the
doctor is his family.  And what do you mean they are family?
But Laila was sure that Yujung had no
relatives.  Does this mean
the company did not investigate the matter
properly?  So, can I
meet with the doctor?  Taking a
closer look, the mentalist saw a resemblance to the
boy Yejo.  And let them meet?
It would be quite a show if they
really are a family.  What kind of despair will
Kan Jeong fall into when he finds himself in
such a dire situation?   Well
then, shall we go?  This is how all of my mother's dreams
were confirmed.  But how did Jehu end
up here?  However, instead of answering, the son
rushed to his mother and began to examine
her mutilated face.  Yujung's body began to
shake even more from fear.  For what?  What do you mean
?  How did the son find out about this place?
Since I couldn't get word from
you, then no, Ju, you can't
be here.
What are you talking about and what's wrong with you?  At that moment,
hysterical laughter cut through the air.  After all,
Layla finally understood why the doctor was
so resistant to her ability.  But
what to do?  She wanted to hide it so desperately
, but alas, it didn't work.  Then
the mother, in hysterics, promised
to tell everything, if only Gio would be released, and
then, with tears in her eyes, began
to ask her son to forgive her.  After all, it's because of
her.  It was only because of her that he fell into this
trap.  However, naturally, Laila had no
plans to let anyone go.  She
was also very interested to see her
son’s reaction after his own
mother forgot about him.  But isn't it
great?  Is this your doing?  It's because of you that my
mother is in this state.  Yeah.  I'm going to keep
going until her brain stops
functioning completely, and so should you
.  But then the mentalist felt
threatened, and then the enraged Ju
threw her into the wall at full speed.
So much so that the girl
broke through it.  What the [ __ ]?  The question arises.
Looking at her son, the mother was taken aback.  But
let him wait a little longer.  I will
definitely get you out of here.  This is
news that Yujong's son has been
awakened.  True, Layla didn’t have
a second to be surprised, because she blinked
once more, and the contents of her head
remained on the same wall.  Realizing that
things were taking a serious turn, the girl
jumped back and used her strength.  An
explosion occurred at the main character's location.
[ __ ], how did this puppy even have
enough courage?  And again the diva's wound
relaxed, because Ju was unharmed and was
already more vile and for the second time launched the
[ __ ] to study the structure of the concrete wall.
Crap.  Who the hell is he?  But the
fool would have known that in front of her was a student of
Kaidan Break himself.  I think she wasn't so sarcastic
and was more worried about how to
get out of the facility alive.  Okay,
baby, I underestimated you.  Now we
will fight like adults.
The air began to fill with a disgusting
energy, but even so, Ju was faster,
so he interrupted the
mentalist's abilities and prescribed her some
preventative measures.
The madam tried to drive the puppy away
by erupting with force from herself.  However, no matter how hard she
tried, her attacks were too
slow, so what followed was
Ju's charged fist that landed on her skinny stomach.  And
this time, Layla received
quite significant damage.  Phew, well, I
guess that's the end.  The mother hurried to find out if her
son was okay.  And yes, that’s how it is.  Well,
she was fine too, which meant we could have
gone back home, if not for
one thing.  Joe's eyes took on an unnatural
color.  I never thought that children these
days could fight like that.  Layla didn't
lose, but besides that, she was still
able to penetrate the guy's mind.  Where the
hell did this puppy come from anyway?   It's just hard to
believe that their organization didn't get
wind of such a young
talent.  Yujung tried
to bring her son to his senses by screaming, but she can
scream as much as she wants.  His mind is already
locked in illusion.  Ah, thank you, Yujung, for
such great material to
experiment with.  A child with such
outstanding abilities.
Laila will treat him very carefully
.
No, what's wrong?  She got me.  Shut up
already.  However, Jo will never allow anyone to raise a hand against her mother
.  A powerful
discharge from the eye pierced the mentalist's body,
painting the corridor bright blue.
Thanks to him, another wall crumbled
due to a collision with Laila.  But
this time the [ __ ] definitely won't
come to her senses quickly.  And yet it was
dangerous.  It always amazes me how
knowledgeable Kaidan is when it comes to fighting against the
Awakened.  After all, it was he who told Ju
how to properly fight the
mentalists.  All thanks to one clever
ability.  Just pretend to be
trapped and then beat the hell out of your enemy
before he gets wind of it.  This
ability suits you perfectly.  Yes,
if it weren't for Kaidan, the main character
would have fallen under the influence
of the technilay long ago.  He was distracted from Razdumi by the
tearful voice of his mother, who was rushing
to check on her son’s condition.  Don't worry,
Mom, I'm really fine.  Let's
get out of here already.  However, the heartfelt conversation
was interrupted by security guards who came running at the sound of the struggle and
immediately released everyone one by one
.  Mother only had time to
feel her body
shudder sharply, but not from the bullets.  Ju pulled her away
, causing the men
to widen their eyes.  After all, the guy stopped and
caught each of their bullets, and then,
without much effort, sent the trio to
rest.  Well, now it's definitely time to
leave.  Grabbing his mother, Ju
hurried to the exit.  Later, the entire center
was in an uproar.  Now the bespectacled
guard ordered everyone to
find the boy and Doctor Yujong at all costs.  And
he still hasn't gotten over the fact that
Elila got beat up too.  So what are you
staring at?  Do you want me to rip your eyes out
?  Contact headquarters immediately.  We must
catch this puppy and that [ __ ] at any cost
.  This [ __ ] couple will beg
for death when I torture them.  But then,
unexpectedly, a meteorite landed on the territory
.  No, it is a person, but who is he
?  The dust settled, and the duo immediately
realized that it was Kaidan himself standing in front of them.
Why is he here like this?  And what are you going to
do with my student?  Stop, why is
that kid doing this?  Just dare
to touch him with your finger.  Then a colossal bolt of
lightning struck the research center.
And in its light one could see the
last thing that was remembered from its
workers.  These are their silhouettes.  Later, Yujo
was put to bed, all under the close
supervision of his son and Kartain.  By the way, here comes
Kaidan.  But where the hell was he
?  Ah, yes, the man just
got some fresh air.  What's more important now is the
condition of Zhu's mother.  She hasn't
woken up yet.  She definitely doesn't have any
complications.  And no, of course not.  Kartain
healed her as best as his abilities
allowed.  But a traumatized brain and
mind are beyond the healer's control, which
only made the son even more worried
.  Zhu still couldn’t understand what
his mother was doing in that place and why she
ended up in such a situation.  The
protagonist told the story of Lyle, a strange
man who injected himself with something and
received a power similar to that of an awakened being,
which naturally caused confusion among the
men.  Suddenly, Yujo woke up and
said that the guard had
injected himself with a narcotic that would make him
wake up.  And oh my god, that means mom is
okay.  Fortunately, yes.  Thanks to
the gentleman in white for curing her.  But
instead of bowing, let the woman
tell about the place where she worked.  And there
they researched ways to create
artificial awakened ones.  But
why?  This is prohibited.  And why did
mom end up in a place like this anyway?
She always claimed that she
worked for a pharmaceutical company.
Silence in response.  Then it dawned on Joe.   Did
mother really take a risk because of
him?  Well, not quite.  In the past, Yujeong did
n't know that her son's ability was the
power of an awakened being.  She was just
trying to find a cure.  Thinking that
the boy was simply very fast, she didn't
realize the pressure
such abnormal speed put on his
body.  However, I still thought it was
bad.  And it would have been dangerous for anyone to find out
about Ju’s abilities.  So
Yuzhon worked diligently for the
pharmaceutical company Esh lekarstva,
but then she received an offer from
some company.  They said they were
conducting research that would unlock
human potential and asked if the
woman would participate.
Therefore, this institution has
been studying awakening abilities for a long time.
Carten's guess turned out to be correct.
At first, Yuzhong didn't know what exactly
this place was.  As people had said,
she believed that this was simply a new
attempt to discover the limits of human
capabilities.  She thought that this
way she could find a cure for Joe.  In
a company, the more research an employee conducts
, the higher his status.
Eventually, Yujung realized that they were
conducting experiments there.  Do I understand correctly that
the experiments were conducted on people?  This question made the
protagonist's eyes pop out of their sockets.
But to his great misfortune, his mother gave a
positive answer.  Much of
the data at the research center was
collected from experiments that,
yes, were conducted on humans.  When her John was
first admitted to secret
research, she was presented with hundreds of
flasks containing frozen bodies of the
awakened.  There she was greeted by
one of the top brass.  He said that
the woman had been chosen.  Together with her,
the company will observe the future of
humanity that they will give birth to.  Yujung did
n't know who was in charge of all the
research.  All she knew was
that this company had
enormous influence and had
several branches.  Therefore, she could no longer
leave that place calmly.  However,
after much deliberation, the decision was
made.  The woman intended to save at
least one person from among those who were
used there as
research subjects.  That's how Yujeong began
her rescue operation.  Then it
becomes clear that at some
point it was declassified.  The doctor
fabricated death reports on subjects due to
supposed accidents during
experiments, and then helped them
escape.  It would be
impossible to do this alone.  So
several colleagues who shared
Yujung's views signed up to be assistants.
Everything went smoothly for several years, but recently she was
caught.  Ju suggested returning home,
since it would be difficult to capture mother there.
However, she couldn't do that.  Since
the company knows who betrayed them, they
will try to catch her at any cost.  And
since they now have information
that she also has a son,
returning home would be the most reckless
decision.  But what to do then?  And then
Kaidan made a joke, like, he, like,
well, blew up that base, in short.  Everyone was surprised
except Kartain.  Why are you
looking at me like that?  I blew up that place, I say,
so as not to leave any witnesses who would
know about Dzhu.  And somewhere in a gloomy
office sat an equally gloomy blond man.
From the monitor screen, a worker told him
that the I9 research complex had been
completely wiped off the face of the earth after the
Awakened One's attack.  Who attacked him?
Kaidanbreak.  And there is
proof of this.  At the scene of the incident, it is
clearly visible that the complex was
destroyed by a powerful
electrical discharge.  No further damage
was caused.  Clear.  Then the subordinate
must understand something.  He shouldn't
send a reconnaissance team there.  We must not let
anyone know about this.
It was necessary to make sure that nothing would ever remain on the site of the
complex.
Upon hearing the order, the employee cut off contact with
the director.  That same night, two men
went out to discuss what to do next.   Does
n't Kaidan want to find out who these
people are doing the experiments?  But why would he
need them?  Wait, what?  So
he doesn't give a damn who
Yujung worked for?  Oh, it looks like the doctor almost got
caught.  I don't care who they are.  If
I had hesitated, Ju's information might have
leaked to the outside world, so
eliminating them was the best solution.  And
now everything fell into place.  Although this is
even brilliant.  Suddenly the men
felt someone's strength.
Aion was realized in the room.  The first thing he
asked about the doctor's condition.  And overall
she's fine because Mr. Carten
took care of her.  Clear.  By the way, as
Dark One thinks, Jui came here and would
like to know the truth.  John, that's exactly it.  And his
mother told him everything.  Wait a minute.  Hyun is
familiar with her.  Kaidan also noted that
from the first time he met Aion, the latter
looked as if he had escaped from somewhere.
So, that center is somehow connected with him?
It turned out that yes.  After all, it was Doctor
Kanyu Dzhon who helped him escape from that
cursed place.  And was Hyun really
one of the test subjects?  Unfortunately, yes.  But the
doctor gave Dark his freedom.  And just
when she came to Ju for the
last time, then Yona realized that
she had a son.  Since then, the criminal
had been keeping an eye on her, but at the moment
she was captured, he was not there
.  Ju remembered how his mother
told him about her unsuccessful
attempt to rescue another
test subject, which caused the mind to be cut by
unpleasant memories, when in the past
all the doctors in front of them were like
monsters, wanting only one thing:
to experiment on the boy’s body.   All sorts of
terrible thoughts came into the
heads of these monsters; they subjected
Dark’s body to all possible
tortures and looked at the results with smiles
.  And only one person
showed warmth and care to him.  It was
Dr. Yujong.  Overall,
the woman was not physically harmed.  However, her mind
was severely tortured, so
thanks to Cartain, she is now fast
asleep.  Taking advantage of the moment, Joo asked
Hyun to tell him more about his mother.
Until now, the boy thought that his
mother worked in a pharmaceutical
company.  However, as it turned out, she
was forced to sign a contract with
the people who were so brutally
cultivating skilled awakened ones.  Ju
was confused and, looking at the sleeping
Yujeong, Aion paused,
then said that everything the doctor said was
true.  The hero's mother took on an
impossible task, but understood
it and tried to help the test subjects.  What
would Joe know?  Dr. Kanyu John was the
only person who considered
the test subjects as people in a living hell, where
everyone looked at them as if they were pigs on
whom they could conduct brutal
experiments, where no one cared about the
feelings of the sufferers, where death seemed like
bliss, Mama Jou was a small
ray of hope.  The beam that so brightly
illuminated this damned path.
Morning came, and Yujung sat up
in bed as if scalded.  Having come to her senses a little, she
looked around the empty, brightly lit
room.  Then the son arrived.  Well, did you get enough
sleep, mother?  Yeah, she had
n't slept so well in a long time.  Then Zhou tiredly
laid his head on her shoulder, saying that
when he learned that he was
awakened, he had his
own goal.  Having met the teacher, I
realized that there was nothing
strange about me, that I didn’t need to be
afraid anymore.  Now I can live a full
life without worrying about anyone
finding out about my quirks.  And by the way, I
finally have some friends.  They are
so much fun to be with.  And so that mother knows, in the
world of the awakened there is a rating that
includes only the strongest people from all over the
world.  True, to do this you have to go through some
pretty tough tests.  However, once you
become part of the top 100, your
influence status will increase significantly among others.
So Ju decided to become stronger.  Why?
He himself would like to know this.
Take Kaidan, for example.  Respected even
among the top ten awakened ones in the world.
He is an amazing person, so Zhou
wants to become as awakened as
he is.  What is clear?  The baby who
was afraid to even go outside finally
grew up, but his mother was still unable to
help him.  Mom, what do you want to
do?  This question took the women
by surprise.  Oh, by the way, while she was sleeping,
Aion came to them.  So what?  So, he
told Joe everything.  Hearing this,
Yujeong's heart sank, as she still considered
herself to be to blame for the suffering of the test subjects.
But no, how could mother not understand that
she became a ray of hope for them,
because with all her heart she wanted to help them.
However, now the time has come for her to choose her
own path.  From such speeches, tears
involuntarily appeared in the
mother’s eyes.  You had to
sacrifice a lot for me.  Now I
want you to take this burden of
responsibility off your shoulders and do what you enjoy
most.  This boy named
Ju has really grown up a lot.  Upon
returning, the heroes were joyfully greeted by
the kittens.  Even Caden got groped.
Gradually they began to put the house in
order.  Cleaning, cleaning up poop and
feeding the furry ones.  It's still so
good to be back home.  But Jue is really okay
.  Yeah.  He felt
relieved because his mother had found something she
wanted to do.  Yujeona told
her son that there was a place where
people who shared her views gathered.  Even though it was
hard to believe.  Since there were
many other laboratories scattered around the world
similar to that complex, there
were people who wanted to help those
who had fallen into the clutches of mad scientists.  And
the woman wanted to look after those
who needed help.  Then the main
character hugged his mother tighter and said
that he understood her.  That's how they
parted again.  But now the boy is sure that
everything is fine with his mother.  And if that’s the case, then there
really is nothing to worry about.
"What? The light's on!"  Suddenly
a group of friends showed up, and they were also
happy about Zhu's return home.  Why did
n't he write that he was back?  And did
you meet your mother?  And yes, yes, everything
went great.  And a huge thank you to the guys for
looking after the kittens.  But
no thanks needed.  They would have
done it anyway.  By the way, Zhu isn't
aware of the news yet.  The Flame rookies decided to
take on the International
Academy students.  It's all because of Flame's attack in the
past.  However, the conflict was
resolved.  Everyone agreed to a
compromise so that their newcomers would fight
among themselves.  Honestly, it sounded a bit
suspicious.  In short, going to
war with Flame was dangerous, because within
this organization there are many powerful
awakened ones, and the top generally
consists of several members of the world
ten.  If war does start, it will
turn into a real disaster.  Therefore, the
organization's members are now preparing,
and it is likely that the top ten will represent the academy
.  Jisok already asked Lee about
this.  They haven't yet decided
who will fight, because the rules
could still change.  Later, Joe lay
in thought.  I wonder what Kaidan
thinks about the news?  Well, it seems like a
good idea.  So what?  But Flame was the one who
started the conflict.  Strength, small.
You need the strength to hold another
person accountable.  do you get it?  Well,
yes, that sounds logical.  But does not an
international organization possess
this power?  Hmm, how can I say it better?   The
International Association is a
collection of awakened people from all over the world.
Because of this, it should be stronger than
organizations like Flame.  However,
the association will not go against them with all
its might.  After all, if she suffers,
who will take her place?  Most likely,
the organizations that are part of it will try
to absorb it while it is weakened.   It is
in such harsh realities that they
exist.  Now the little one understands that in order to
protect someone, you need strength.  In the
human world, everything works on the same
principle, but in the world of the awakened, it is
simply more pronounced.  This leads to
the conclusion that the conflict between the students
will cause less harm to the organization, and all the
pre-agreed conditions between the two
organizations will be fulfilled
after the duels.  It all sounded damn
hard to understand, but if you generalize, you
just need to be strong, like
Kaidan, for example.  So I quickly got off
my butt and went to practice.   If
I see you're slacking off, I'll give you a slap on the wrist.
And now the usual routine has returned.
Training, meditation, walking and more
training until exhaustion.  Until,
for some reason, everyone was called to the shinha, where the main
character was finally able to see the beautiful
Yujiyon.  But why did they call the guys here?
They've probably already heard about the
confrontation between Flame and the international.   And so
the results were announced.  Right.  As
expected, the guys from the
top ten of the International Academy competed.
So, they lost, and some of
the students even received serious
injuries, which will make it difficult for them, as
awakened ones, to fight in the future
.  Our heroes
were overcome with a quiet horror at this news.  Jion didn't know who
exactly won and who lost.  But the fact is
that most of the top ten lost
.  Or maybe, well, he knows how
Leah is.  But Miss Eresby was defeated
and lost one eye.  Now Ju
thought even more about the director's words.
Did the guys really fight to the last?
But he should understand that this was not a simple
conflict, but a battle defending
the interests of both sides.  Ilie Eresby
may have been luckier than others.
The same Arthur was defeated and lost his
arm.  Laura Jenson actually died like that.
However, it was worth giving ten its due.
Even as students, they courageously
accepted the fact that this could
be their last fight.  And yet it was very
unexpected that the Academy's top ten
lost.  Oh yeah, there were rumors that
Duke Grain, who betrayed the association, played a major role in Flame's victory
.  That's when
the guys were even more taken aback.  What
did Duke do?  Most likely, he passed on
detailed information about the
academy's top ten.  After all, during the battle,
Flame's newcomers handled the
Ten's abilities so well that it would have been
impossible without a detailed knowledge of
their techniques.  And since Duke studied at the same
academy, they understood each other
better than anyone else.  Therefore, it is
obvious that he leaked information about his
former comrades.  But
the guys got even more angry at this freak when they found out that it was
he who cut off Arthur’s hand.  [ __ ], I
can't believe it was such an idiot.
Slamming the door, Jiseok hurried
away, leaving the three friends.
In general, this skirmish will not affect Korea,
because Flame formally
apologized for
unintentionally dragging a Korean into this
conflict last time.  But, obviously, these apologies
were not without reason.  First of all, Flame
recognized Mr. Kaidan and his
student.  After all, in a situation where they
already have a conflict with the international
association, it would be burdensome for them
to turn them into their enemies.  Ju told the news of the
defeat of the ten to his elders.
And Kaidan was surprised, because for their
age, the ten had good skills,
how could they lose.  But why is
this news to Red?  Just remember
that Flame is merciless to children, and
everything immediately becomes obvious.  And that's a
fair point.  Ju, I wonder
what this means?  And the fact is that Flame will do anything to
increase their strength.  That's why
in such a place they force even children
to train mercilessly, as if they were
already adults.  And this organization
uses previously untested methods,
so many guys die even in the
process.  Now that the association
has lost, Flame must be busy.
After all, all their time is spent on eliminating the
consequences.  They have probable casualties
.  Which was not worth denying.  Knowing Flame,
even a fight between newbies could result in
losses.  After all, the goal of these newcomers
was to speak on behalf of their
organization.  Then, in a low voice, Joe
said that Arthur had lost his arm.  And this is the
guy who was friendly with the Koreans
.  Yeah.  Crap.  Again this little guy
with a sad expression.  Hayden will go and
feed the kittens better.  So the carteyns
will clean up their poop.  Staying on her day, the main
character remembered how he was able to become friends
with Arthur and how he got his
number.  So maybe it's worth
calling now?  But it seemed like my friend wasn't going to pick up the phone
.  It is not surprising.  Who
would answer in such a state?  Um, Suju,
what did you take?  Why are you calling?  He said he would get in touch
, but he never called.  Although it's
obvious why Zhu called.  He's
heard it already, right?  Yeah.  Damn, how quickly
rumors spread.  But what about
Arthur's hand?  How should I say it?  It's unusual,
of course, but it's livable.  It's better than
dying.  Only Brian was more
angry at that idiot Duke.  However, now is
probably not the time to talk about this.
Why did Ju dial anyway?  It's unlikely that he would
just remain silent on the phone.  I'm sorry, I
called because I was worried, but
now I don't even know what to say.  And then
Arthur remembered how his father yelled at him
after he lost.  Fool, do you even know
what you've done?  Not only
was the Bryan family's reputation damaged, but
our influence was also greatly damaged.
So even such a friendly, slightly
strange call from Zhu was heartwarming.
Therefore, there is no need for a friend to apologize.  He has already
done a lot.  Let him better
tell how the others are doing.  In order.
That's great.  Suddenly, Arthur
wanted to see those losers,
so the protagonist invited him to
Korea once he recovered.
The conversation then continued on its own, but at the same
time, Jion was completely
perplexed.  It's all because of a sharp call from
Flame.  They wanted to invite a newcomer
named Zhou to join them, so afterward the
director looked tensely at Night
City.  And the question is, will she tell
Ju about this call?  After all, judging by the
guy’s behavior, it’s unlikely that he will refuse.  And
Jion understood this perfectly well.  However,
Shinhwa has no right to stop him.   A
new day has dawned.  Poor Kostratus
couldn't get a good night's sleep.  And all because of
two thick-headed people obsessed with fighting and
training.  Today, Joe was hitting the punching
bag like crazy, but that wasn't enough.  Why are you so [ __ ]
slow?  Then the main character
increased his pressure even more.  They will have to
train even harder today
than usual.  From the outside it looks
funny, but given the fact that there is no
way to contain Ju's power, Kaidan
himself forces him to control his
ability.  And now all training
takes place in a similar manner.  What about your
attack power?  Are you not concentrating?   Do
you think you can take down your enemy with
such a weak force?  Pull yourself together, damn it
.  Come on even harder.  At that moment, the
main character really focused, so
much so that he almost knocked over the teacher and
Grusha.  The blow caused
silence.  Ju was ready to continue, but
enough, he tried very hard.  Now maybe
Pokimiri too.  Looking at the remains of the pear,
Kaidan remembered that he would have to wrap it more carefully from now on
, and Krasava's student
finally began to use force much
more consistently and freely.  It is immediately obvious
that his ability is gradually becoming
stronger.  And the skills that Gunsik taught him are
definitely improving.  And Jules
supported the teacher's remark, because he himself
was surprised at how useful the
director's strength turned out to be in close combat.   It
allows you to hit an enemy
using much less force, but they are
more effective when you get close.  And when
you hit an enemy, the recoil is
less, thanks to which the main character could
easily carry out more powerful attacks.
And while the control that Gonsik taught him
isn't capable of accumulating power in a
teleawakened person, it's still an
excellent technique that will allow him to more
effectively utilize the many
movements required for close combat.
So with this, Joe needs to train
even harder.  Then the guy started
meditating, and Kaidan was amazed to himself.
This racer.  At first, Break thought the
old man was just teaching Ju a good
technique, but it turned out to be what he
needed.  And Kartain was no less
surprised.  Anyone who fights in close
combat would like to
master such a technique at all costs.  By the way,
Gonsik didn’t happen to teach the kid the same
technique that he himself uses.
But how would Kaidan know?  He had
been fighting with him for a long time.  But this is definitely not control of the
forces that are used in Bekha.
Therefore, most likely, Starper
created this technique himself, created something
based on his experience.  But then
why did Gonsik teach this to Ju?  What the hell is
this
old man up to?  And when the sun was already
setting behind the horizon, a
guest, Yudzhiyon, arrived at the house and
asked to give her some time for a one-on-one conversation
.  She actually
sent a message to Ju in advance, but since he
didn’t read it, she decided to come in person.  And oh,
how awkward it turned out.
The guy didn't notice because he was training.  After all, the
main character has only recently started
training, and he has a long way to go.
By the way, what did Nuna want to talk about?
That's when the girl's face took on a serious
expression.  She reported that Flame had
sent a message that they were not
inviting Zhu to their place.  But why?   The
official reason given was that they
wanted to be associated with
Kaiden's student.  They also added that they would like to
resolve the recent unpleasant
situation.  And looking at the guy’s thoughtful face
, the chairwoman said honestly: she would
like him to refuse.  Of course,
he was officially invited, but it is
still dangerous.  Even if Jou is the
great Kaidan's disciple, no one knows what
might happen there.  You know, I do
n't want that either.  Then you, however, cannot help but do it
.  I really don't want to
go to them.  And what happened recently,
and yet Flame did invite
Gidden's student.  And the teacher always repeats one
thing.  Jeu, as his follower,
will always be surrounded by danger.
Says the guy could get into
trouble.  That is why he
should be prepared for such situations.
Zhou has always been proud to be
Kaidan's student, so he's not going to
avoid it by saying it's dangerous.
As his student, I will accept this
responsibility.  These words had
an effect on the director, but she knew that this was
exactly what she should expect.  In any
case, she apologized for not
teaching Ju to feel and for judging in her
own way.  And while the two continued their
pleasant conversation, Caden, looking at this,
tensed up.  Although, what is this he?  Zhu is already
right.  The moment he became his
disciple, a lot of responsibility fell on him
.  Kaidan should be
glad that the protagonist doesn't
avoid this.  However, he only clicked his tongue and
went upstairs.  So he just decided to leave
?  Shut your mouth, castrato.
Meanwhile, in distant cold lands, the
Duke swarmed.  Well, Sakhyon
recently heard something interesting.
Apprentice Kaidan was invited to Aflame.
You can watch the other 15 parts on
Boost or in the paid Telegram channel.
So, guys, I want to apologize right away for the
delay.  It's all because I recently
had surgery and after it I
couldn't get out of bed for about 6 days.  By the way,
the operation went without any problems at all.
The problem was precisely the withdrawal symptoms after
spinal anesthesia.  It just so happened that it took my
body a very long time to let go.  And
since I am the one writing the sheet, I simply physically did not have time to finish
it on time.  But luckily it
seems to be ready to work again now,
so don't worry, everything will be
as usual from now on.  At least I
hope so.  Thanks for watching.  Don't
forget to like and
comment.  And for you, as usual,
Saidjst spoke.  Bye.  y